Guide to the Frank Richard Oastler Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photograph Albums, 1912-1935; Series I; 54.2' (69 boxes)
  - 1923
    - Mount Hood, Crater Lake, Cascade Mountains, [1923] (Box 31, Folder 31)
      Includes photographs by L.D. Lindsley, Gurr Photo, and Cross & Dimmitt
    - Saskatchewan, Canada. Mount Rainier and climb to summit. Cascade Mountains, [1923] (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - 1924
    - Colorado and Mohave Desert. Grand Canyon, and California, [1924] (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Bryce Canyon, Zion Canyon, New Brunswick, Yosemite, [1924] (Box 34, Folder 34)
      Two photographs of a moose fording a river laid in loose
    - Yosemite, Redwoods, Olympic Mountains, Alberta, Canada, [1924] (Box 35, Folder 35)
      Maps of California laid in loose. Includes photographs by E.R. Freeman Photo, and Winter & Pond Co., Juneau
    - High Sierras, Colorado, and Mohave Desert, [1924] (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - 1925
    - Spring: Eastern Flowers, [1925] (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Spring: Eastern Flowers, [1925] (Box 38, Folder 38)
      Hand-colored photograph of a river scene with boat laid in loose
    - Devil's Garden, Winslow Castles, Blue Mountains, Arch Canyon, White Canyon, [1925] (Box 39, Folder 39)
      Five photographs of fawns laid in loose, with Mrs. Oastler's notes on itinerary of trip. Includes photographs by Smith's Photo
    - Mount Rainier and Yellowstone, [1925] (Box 40, Folder 40)
      Eleven photographs of bears, and one of Mt. Rainier laid in loose
    - Colorado River, Bryce Canyon, and Yosemite, [1925] (Box 41, Folder 41)
      Mrs. Oastler's holograph notes on itinerary of trip laid in loose
    - Olympic Mountains and Yellowstone National Park, [1925-1926] (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - 1926
    - Jasper National Park and Crater Lake, [1926] (Box 43, Folder 43)
      Photographs of mountain in Jasper National Park laid in loose
    - Glacier National Park, [1926] (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - Idaho, Isle Royale, and Yellowstone, [1926-1928] (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - 1927
    - Spring: Eastern Flowers, [1927] (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Alaska and Yellowstone, [1927] (Box 47, Folder 47)
      Two photographs laid in loose
    - Alaska, [1927] (Box 48, Folder 48)
      Manuscript maps and photographs laid in loose
    - Alaska, [1927] (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - 1928
    - Redwoods, Grand Canyon, Zion National Park, Bryce National Park, Sequoia, Yosemite, Lassen, [1928] (Box 50, Folder 50)
    - Bear River Marshes of Utah, [1928] (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - 1929
    - Bryce Canyon, [1929] (Box 52, Folder 52)
      Newspaper clipping laid in loose
    - Mount Rainier National Park, Rocky Mountain National Park, Grand Teton National Park, Zion National Park, Mesa Verde National Park, [1929] (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - Charleston, S.C.; Quill Lake, Saskatchewan, Canada; Isle Royale, Michigan; Yellowstone National Park; Grand Canyon, [1929] (Box 54, Folder 54)
      Photograph of spanish moss laid in loose
  - 1930
    - Cobbs Island, Virginia; Isle Royale, Michigan; Bear River, Utah; Bird Island, Great Salt Lake, Utah; Banff, Alberta, Canada; Yellowstone, [1930 May-Sep] (Box 55, Folder 55)
      Photograph of a flower laid in loose
    - Canadian Rocky Mountains, Alberta, Canada, [1930 Aug-Sep] (Box 56, Folder 56)
  - 1931
    - Smoky Mountains, Isle Royale, and Glacier Park, [1931] (Box 57, Folder 57)
      Photograph of deer laid in loose, with Christmas greetings on back from Mr. & Mrs. Joseph S. Dixon, Berkeley, California. Includes photographs by Jim Thompson Co. Knoxville, and Thieman [?], Kalispell, Montana
    - Pack Train Trip around Mount Rainier, [1931] (Box 58, Folder 58)
    - Florida, Texas, and Louisiana, [1931] (Box 59, Folder 59)
      Photograph of an American egret [?] laid in loose
  - 1932-1933
    - Trumpeter Swan at Red Rock Lake; Yellowstone National Park; Grand Teton National Park; Bear River Marsh, Utah, [1932-1933] (Box 60, Folder 60)
    - Canadian Rockies and Cypress Swamp, [1933] (Box 61, Folder 61)
  - 1934
    - Isle Royale and Yellowstone, [1934] (Box 62, Folder 62)
  - 1935
    - Stikine River and Cassiar Mountains, Alaska, [1935] (Box 63, Folder 63)
      Includes photographs by Winter & Pond, Juneau, and T. Davis
    - Alaska, Yellowstone Park, and Glacier Park, [1935] (Box 64, Folder 64)
  - UNDATED
    - Eastern Flowers and Central Park, undated (Box 65, Folder 65)
    - Spring in the East, undated (Box 66, Folder 66)
      First leaf inscribed in Mrs. Oastler's handwriting: "I think these pictures were taken in Westchester County, Bronx Park, and near Greenwich, Conn."
    - Spring in the East, undated (Box 67, Folder 67)
    - Spring and Winter in the East, undated (Box 68, Folder 68)
  - LOOSE ITEMS REMOVED FROM ALBUMS
    - Typescript description of trip, printed maps, photographic postcard of the Glacier Park Hotel removed from Box 3, 1913 Glacier National Park, Album I (Box 69, Folder 69)
    - Printed maps and a letter from Joe Warner, hunter and guide, to Dr. Oastler dated 1915 Mar 16, which were previously in the "Maps" envelope at the front of the 1914 Mount Robson Trip, Album I, 1915, undated (Box 69, Folder 70)
    - Printed map previously in the envelope at the front of 1915 Wyoming Album I, undated (Box 69, Folder 71)
  - OTHER PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Glacier Park, Montana. Found with the cut film negatives, 1912-1926 (Box 69, Folder 72)
    - Miscellaneous photographs found with the cut film negatives, undated (Box 69, Folder 73)
    - Formerly Framed Photographs
      Formerly framed photographs of created by Oastler and made into an enlarged photographic print by Robert C. Heinze. The photographs are accompanied by the backing papers as well as a brass plaque originally attached to one of the frames.
      - "Uncle Ned," Bull Moose, Rock Harbor, Isle Royale National Park, Michigan, undated
        Inscription on verso of backing paper "I.R.N.P. No. 2"
      - "Uncle Ned," Bull Moose, Rock Harbor, Isle Royale National Park, Michigan
        Inscription on verso of backing paper "I.R.N.P. No. 3"
      - Squirrel, probably in Isle Royale National Park, Michigan, undated
        Inscription on recto: "3"
      - White Birches, Isle Royale National Park, Michigan, undated
        Inscription on verso of backing paper "I.R.N.P. No. 4"
      - Frog being fed a dragonfly by Mrs. Oastler at Mud Lake, Isle Royale National Park, Michigan
        Inscription on verso: "I.R.N.P. No. 6"
      - Two moose, probably in Isle Royale National Park, Michigan
- Lantern Slides, 1908-1938; Series II; 71' (167 boxes)
  Series II, Lantern Slides, is organized into two subseries: Lantern Slides in Oastler's Classification, and Unclassified Lantern Slides. A card index, housed in ten boxes, provides access to the lantern slides in the first subseries, which are arranged to a classification system, the key to which appears in a bound typescript (box 80). The first letter and number of the classification refers to the place in which the photograph was taken, and for convenience the headings are included here as headings.
  - LANTERN SLIDES IN OASTLER'S CLASSIFICATION
    - Indexes and Related Material
      Card Index
      - Air plant - Bear River, Birds, undated (Box 70, Folder 74)
      - Bear River, Scenic - Canadian Rocky Mountains, Scenic, undated (Box 71, Folder 75)
      - Canadian Rocky Mountains, Scenic - Colorado River Region, Scenic, undated (Box 72, Folder 76)
      - Colorado River Region, Scenic - Ferns, undated (Box 73, Folder 77)
      - Finch - Heron, Black-crowned Night, undated (Box 74, Folder 78)
      - Heron, Blue - Mayflower, undated (Box 75, Folder 79)
      - Meadow rue - New York, Scenic, undated (Box 76, Folder 80)
      - New York, Trees - Sheep, undated (Box 77, Folder 81)
      - Sheep, Dall - Yellowstone Region, Animals, undated (Box 78, Folder 82)
      - Yellowstone Region, Animals - Zygadena, undated (Box 79, Folder 83)
      - Related Material
        - "Classification of Lantern Slides, Frank R. Oastler Memorial Collection at Yale University," bound typescript, 1938 Sep (Box 80, Folder 84)
        - Oastler Collection sign indicating the lantern slides were hand colored by Mildred Petry, undated
    - Lantern Slides
      Alaska
      - A2 Ab3 1 - A2 Am7 2, 1927-1935, undated (Box 81, Folder 85)
      - A2 Am7 3 - A2 Bg9 2, 1927, undated (Box 82, Folder 86)
      - A2 Bg9 3 - A2 Mf4 Sh2, 1927-1935, undated (Box 83, Folder 87)
      - A2 Mf9 ts1 - A2 S2 6, 1927, undated (Box 84, Folder 88)
      - A2 S2 7 - A2 S3 4, 1927-1935, undated (Box 85, Folder 89)
      - A2 S3 5 - A2 S3 39, 1927-1935, undated (Box 86, Folder 90)
      - A2 S3 40 - A2 S3 75, 1927 (Box 87, Folder 91)
      - A2 S3 76 - A2 S3 108, 1927, undated (Box 88, Folder 92)
      - A2 S3 109 - A2 S3 127, 1921, undated (Box 89, Folder 93)
        Missing: A2 S3 109
      - Arches National Monument
        - A4 Ad3 a1 - A4 S2 17, 1925
        - A4 S2 18 - A4 S2 52, 1925, undated (Box 90, Folder 94)
        - A4 S2 53 - A4 S2 55, 1925-1932, undated (Box 91, Folder 95)
      - Bear River Region
        - B3 Am85 1 - B3 Bc9 l4, 1928-1932, undated
        - B3 Bc9 l5 - B3 Bd8 rh20, 1928-1932, undated (Box 92, Folder 96)
        - B3 Bd8 rh21 - B3 Be3 s22, 1928-1930, undated (Box 93, Folder 97)
        - B3 Bg2 1 - B3 Bg9 c10, 1928-1932, undated (Box 94, Folder 98)
        - B3 Bg9 c11 - B3 Bh3 t5, 1928-1930, undated (Box 95, Folder 99)
        - B3 Bh3 t6 - B3 Bo8 s2, 1928-1930, undated (Box 96, Folder 100)
        - B3 Bp3 w1 - B3 Bt2 b16, 1920-1932, undated (Box 97, Folder 101)
        - B3 Bt2 f1 - B3 S1 4, 1928-1930, undated (Box 98, Folder 102)
        - B3 S1 5 - B3 S1 23, 1928-1932 (Box 99, Folder 103)
      - British Columbia
        - B7 Ag5 rm1 - B7 S3 4, 1935
      - Bryce Canyon National Park
        - B8 Fc5 b1 - B8 Fl6 Se2, 1924-1925
        - B8 Fp3 p1 - B8 S2 1, 1924-1925, undated (Box 100, Folder 104)
        - B8 S2 2 - B8 S2 42, 1924-1925, undated (Box 101, Folder 105)
        - B8 S2 43 - B8 Tp4 y1, 1924-1925, undated (Box 102, Folder 106)
      - California
        - C1 Bc7 1 - C1 Ts3 11, 1923-1924, undated
        - C1 Ts3 12 - C1 Ts3 30, 1924, undated (Box 103, Folder 107)
      - Canadian Rocky Mountains
        - C2 Ab3 1 - C2 Ab4 3, 1923-1926, undated
        - C2 Ab4 4 - C2 Ag6 1, 1921-1930, undated (Box 104, Folder 108)
          Missing: C2 Ad8 m1 C2 Ad8 m2 C2 Ae5 1 C2 Ae5 2 C2 Ae5 6 C2 Ag5 rm1 C2 Ag5 rm2 C2 Ag5 rm4
        - C2 Ah7 1 - C2 As6 rm25, 1921-1933, undated (Box 105, Folder 109)
          Missing: C2 Ap5 1 C2 As6 rm1 C2 As6 rm2
        - C2 As6 rm26 - C2 Bc7 5, 1923-1929, undated (Box 106, Folder 110)
        - C2 Bc7 6 - C2 Bg88 p7, 1921-1929, undated (Box 107, Folder 111)
        - C2 Bg88 p8 - C2 Bp3 w14, 1913-1933, undated (Box 108, Folder 112)
        - C2 Bp4 w1 - C2 Fa7 p3, 1921-1933, undated (Box 109, Folder 113)
        - C2 Fa8 y1 - C2 Fo5 wr1, 1920-1933, undated (Box 110, Folder 114)
        - C2 Fp1 1 - C2 S2 7, 1921-1933, undated (Box 111, Folder 115)
          Missing: C2 S1 1
        - C2 S2 8 - C2 S2 43, 1920-1933, undated (Box 112, Folder 116)
        - C2 S2 44 - C2 S2 78, 1920-1921, undated (Box 113, Folder 117)
        - C2 S2 79 - C2 S2 115, 1914-1926, undated (Box 114, Folder 118)
        - C2 S2 116 - C2 S3 7, 1920-1933, undated (Box 115, Folder 119)
          Missing: C2 S2 137
        - C2 S3 8 - C2 S3 45, 1930-1933, undated (Box 116, Folder 120)
        - C2 S3 46 - C2 S3 84, 1926-1933, undated (Box 117, Folder 121)
        - C2 S3 85 - C2 S3 120, 1914-1933, undated (Box 118, Folder 122)
        - C2 S3 121 - C2 S3 152, 1914, undated (Box 119, Folder 123)
        - C2 S3 153 - C2 S3 186, 1920-1921, undated (Box 120, Folder 124)
        - C2 S3 187 - C2 S3 222, 1921, undated (Box 121, Folder 125)
        - C2 S3 223 - C2 S3 255, 1921, 1931 (Box 122, Folder 126)
        - C2 S3 256 - C2 S3 291, 1921-1931, undated (Box 123, Folder 127)
        - C2 S3 292 - C2 S3 325, 1926, undated (Box 124, Folder 128)
        - C2 S3 326 - C2 S3 365, 1921-1926, undated (Box 125, Folder 129)
          Missing: C2 S3 359-19360
        - C2 S3 366 - C2 S3 402, 1923 (Box 126, Folder 130)
        - C2 S3 403 - C2 S3 438, 1923 (Box 127, Folder 131)
        - C2 S3 439 - C2 Ts5 1, 1920-1929, undated (Box 128, Folder 132)
          Missing: C2 T1 1
      - Cascade Mountain Region
        - C3 Bh9 1 - C3 Bj1 C1, 1923, undated
        - C3 Fg2 1 - C3 Ts5 1, 1923, undated (Box 129, Folder 133)
          Missing: C3 T1 1
      - Colorado River Region
        - C5 Ab9 1 - C5 B1, 1922-1928, undated (Box 130, Folder 134)
          Missing: C5 Ac2 b1-b2
        - C5 Bb6 1 - C5 Fb29 1, 1922-1928, undated (Box 131, Folder 135)
        - C5 Fb88 1 - C5 Fc12 o5, 1923-1925, undated (Box 132, Folder 136)
        - C5 Fc12 pe1 - C5 Fl58 w2, 1922-1925, undated (Box 133, Folder 137)
        - C5 Fl58 w3 - C5 Fv28 d1, 1921-1925, undated (Box 134, Folder 138)
        - C5 Fv28 d2 - C5 Ms5 r4, 1922-1925, undated (Box 135, Folder 139)
        - C5 Ms5 r5 - C5 S2 37, 1924-1925, undated (Box 136, Folder 140)
        - C5 S2 38 - C5 S2 74, 1923-1925, undated (Box 137, Folder 141)
        - C5 S2 75 - C5 S2 111, 1923, undated (Box 138, Folder 142)
        - C5 S2 112 - C5 S2 152, 1922-1925, undated (Box 139, Folder 143)
        - C5 S2 153 - C5 S2 191, 1925, undated (Box 140, Folder 144)
        - C5 S2 192 - C5 S2 229, 1922-1924, undated (Box 141, Folder 145)
        - C5 S2 230 - C5 S2 264, 1923, undated (Box 142, Folder 146)
        - C5 S2 265 - C5 S2 304, 1922, undated (Box 143, Folder 147)
        - C5 S2 305 - C5 S2 345, 1922-1923 (Box 144, Folder 148)
        - C5 S2 346 - C5 S2 379, 1922-1923 (Box 145, Folder 149)
        - C5 S2 380 - C5 S3 4, 1922-1925, undated (Box 146, Folder 150)
        - C5 S3 5 - C5 S3 42, 1923-1925 (Box 147, Folder 151)
        - C5 S3 43 - C5 S3 80, 1925 (Box 148, Folder 152)
        - C5 S3 81 - C5 S3 112, 1923-1925, undated (Box 149, Folder 153)
        - C5 S4 1 - C5 S4 33, [1922]-1925, undated (Box 150, Folder 154)
        - C5 S4 34 - C5 Tp1 2, 1922-1925, undated (Box 151, Folder 155)
        - C5 Tp1 3 - C5 Tw4 d3, 1922-1925, undated (Box 152, Folder 156)
      - Connecticut
        - C55 Bc8 s1 - C55 S3 1, 1918-1923, undated (Box 153, Folder 157)
      - Crater Lake National Park
        - C6 Am25 1 - C6 Ts5 2, 1923, undated
      - Florida
        - F5 Ba5 1 - F5 Bl5 3, 1931, undated (Box 154, Folder 158)
        - F5 Bp3 b1 - F5 S3 15, 1929-1931, undated (Box 155, Folder 159)
          Missing: F5 Bp3 b1
        - F5 S3 16 - F5 Tp1 co2, 1931, undated (Box 156, Folder 160)
          Missing: F5 Tm2 3
      - Glacier National Park
        - G4 Ab3 b1 - G4 Ag5 rm1, 1926-1935, undated
        - G4 Ag5 rm2 - G4 Fd12 sa1, 1913-1935, undated (Box 157, Folder 161)
        - G4 Fd8 1 - G4 S1 10, 1926-1935, undated (Box 158, Folder 162)
        - G4 S1 11 - G4 S2 34, 1926-1935, undated (Box 159, Folder 163)
        - G4 S2 35 - G4 S3 4, 1926-1935, undated (Box 160, Folder 164)
          Missing: G4 S2 40
        - G4 S3 5 - G4 S3 41, 1926, undated (Box 161, Folder 165)
          Missing: G4 S3 31
        - G4 S3 42 - G4 S3 79, 1926-1935, undated (Box 162, Folder 166)
        - G4 S3 80 - G4 Tp4 c1, 1912-1935, undated (Box 163, Folder 167)
      - Grand Canyon, Colorado River
        - G6 Aa5 1 - G6 Ad3 m2, 1928-1930, undated
        - G6 Ad3 m3 - G6 S1 11, 1922-1925, undated (Box 164, Folder 168)
          Missing: G6 S1 11
        - G6 S1 12 - G6 S1 43, 1922-1923, undated (Box 165, Folder 169)
        - G6 S1 44 - G6 Ta85 c1, 1925, undated (Box 166, Folder 170)
      - Grand Teton National Park
        - G7 Am7 1 - G7 Am7 2, 1934
        - G7 Am7 3 - G7 S3 1, 1925-1934, undated (Box 167, Folder 171)
      - Gulf of Mexico
        - G9 Be3 a1 - G9 Bh3 m2, 1931, undated
        - G9 Bh4 1 - G9 Bt2 r4, 1931-1934, undated (Box 168, Folder 172)
      - High Sierra Region (including Sequoia and General Grant National Parks and Forest)
        - H4 Ac3 1 - H4 Ad3 5, 1922-1925, undated
        - H4 Ad3 6 - H4 Ad3 20, 1922-1925, undated (Box 169, Folder 173)
        - H4 Ad3 21 - H4 Fc4 y1, 1922-1925, undated (Box 170, Folder 174)
        - H4 Ff 38 1 - H4 Ms5 r1, 1921-1925, undated (Box 171, Folder 175)
          Missing: H4 Fp4 1
        - H4 S2 1 - H4 S3 3, 1921-1928 (Box 172, Folder 176)
        - H4 S3 4 - H4 S3 37, 1921-1924 (Box 173, Folder 177)
        - H4 S3 38 - H4 Ts3 4, 1922-1924, undated (Box 174, Folder 178)
      - Idaho
        - I2 Ad6 1 - I2 Bg88 1, 1922-1926
        - I2 Bg88 2 - I2 S3 9, 1926, undated (Box 175, Folder 179)
        - I2 S3 10 - I2 Th2 1, 1926 (Box 176, Folder 180)
      - Isle Royale, Michigan
        - I8 Af8 s1 - I8 Am7 30, 1926-1934, undated
        - I8 Am7 31 - I8 Bl6 1, 1926-1934, undated (Box 177, Folder 181)
          Missing: I8 Am7 45-47, 50 I8 Bg9 h4
        - I8 Fb8 1 - I8 Ms5 b2, 1932-1934, undated (Box 178, Folder 182)
        - I8 MS6 1 - I8 S3 23, 1926-1934, undated (Box 179, Folder 183)
        - I8 S3 24 - I8 Tb4 w5, 1926-1934, undated (Box 180, Folder 184)
        - I8 Tb4 w6 - I8 Ts5 1, 1934, undated (Box 181, Folder 185)
      - Kaibab Region
        - K2 Ad3 1 - K2 Ad3 m5, 1924-1926, undated
      - Louisiana
        - L6 Bg9 h1 - L6 S3 1, 1931, undated
      - Massachusetts
        - M3 Ac27 1 - M3 S2 1, 1917, undated
      - Mesa Verde National Park
        - M4 Fc12 pc1 - M4 S4 6, 1925, undated
        - M4 S4 7 - M4 S4 20, 1922-1925, undated (Box 182, Folder 186)
      - Mexico
        - M5 Ad3 1 - M5 S2 3, 1923, undated
      - Mississippi
        - M7 Bp3 1 - M7 S1 1, 1931, undated
      - Montana
        - M8 Ac3 1 - M8 As6 rm3, undated
        - M8 As6 rm4 - M8 S2 6, 1912-1933, undated (Box 183, Folder 187)
      - Mount Hood Region
        - M85 Ac3 1 - M85 S2 8, 1923-1926, undated
        - M85 S3 1 - M85 S3 18, 1923, undated (Box 184, Folder 188)
      - Mount Rainier
        - M9 Ab3 1 - M9 As8 b1, 1920-1924, undated
        - M9 Bc88 c1 - M9 Fp43 p1, 1923-1932, undated (Box 185, Folder 189)
        - M9 Fq3 1 - M9 S2 10, 1923-1931, undated (Box 186, Folder 190)
        - M9 S2 11 - M9 S2 45, 1924-1931, undated (Box 187, Folder 191)
        - M9 S2 46 - M9 S2 80, 1920-1932, undated (Box 188, Folder 192)
        - M8 S2 81 - M9 Ts5 4, 1923-1931, undated (Box 189, Folder 193)
      - New Brunswick
        - N3 Ad3 1 - N3 S3 7, 1924, undated (Box 190, Folder 194)
      - New Jersey
        - N4 Bo8 gh1, 1933
      - New Mexico
        - N5 Ab9 1 - N5 Ms5 r1, 1917-1922, undated
        - N5 S1 1 - N5 S2 34, 1917-1923, undated (Box 191, Folder 195)
        - N5 S2 35 - N5 S3 10, 1921, undated (Box 192, Folder 196)
        - N5 S3 11 - N5 Ta85 q1, undated (Box 193, Folder 197)
      - New York (State)
        - N9 Ac27 1 - N9 As8 g1, 1908-1923, undated
        - N9 Bc88 1 - N9 Fa7 p1, 1919-1933, undated (Box 194, Folder 198)
        - N9 Fa7 p2 - N9 Fb9 2, 1919-1926, undated (Box 195, Folder 199)
        - N9 Fb92 1 - N9 Fj1 3, 1918-1933, undated (Box 196, Folder 200)
        - N9 Fj5 1 - N9 Fp3 w3, 1918-1933, undated (Box 197, Folder 201)
        - N9 Fp43 p1 - N9 Fv4 y1, 1918-1925, undated (Box 198, Folder 202)
        - N9 Fv45 1 - N9 S2 2, 1918-1933, undated (Box 199, Folder 203)
        - N9 S2 3 - N9 S3 28, 1910-1933, undated (Box 200, Folder 204)
        - N9 S3 29 - N9 T1 7, 1917-1934, undated (Box 201, Folder 205)
        - N9 T1 8 - N9 Tb3 2, 1919-1926, undated (Box 202, Folder 206)
        - N9 Tb4 1 - N9 Tp5 1, 1920-1926, undated (Box 203, Folder 207)
        - N9 Tp8 1 - N9 Tw4 2, 1919-1925 (Box 204, Folder 208)
      - North Carolina
        - N95 Ar13 1, undated
      - Olympic Region
        - O5 Ab4 1 - O5 S3 4, 1924-1925, undated
        - O5 S3 5 - O5 T1 17, 1924-1925, undated (Box 205, Folder 209)
          Missing: O5 T1 2
        - O5 T1 18 - O5 Ts5 1, 1924-1925, undated (Box 206, Folder 210)
      - Ouray Region (Uncompagre National Forest)
        - O8 S3 1 - O8 S3 3, 1935
      - Pennsylvania
        - P3 S2 1 - P3 S3 4, 1917-1921, undated
      - Rocky Mountain National Park
        - R6 Ab4 1 - R6 S3 7, 1923-1929, undated (Box 207, Folder 211)
      - Smoky Mountain National Park
        - S5 S3 1 - S5 S3 2, undated
      - South Carolina
        - S7 Bh4 l1 - S7 Bs4 b4, 1929-1931, undated
        - S7 Bs4 b5 - S7 To1 b1, 1928-1931, undated (Box 208, Folder 212)
      - Switzerland
        - S9 S2 1 - S9 S3 4, undated
      - Texas
        - T3 Bd8 1 - T3 Bh4 wa7, 1931, undated (Box 209, Folder 213)
        - T3 Bh4 yc1 - T3 S3 5, 1930-1931, undated (Box 210, Folder 214)
      - Virginia
        - V8 Bd8 bl1 - V8 S3 1, 1930-1933, undated (Box 211, Folder 215-)
      - Yellowstone National Park and Region
        - Y3 Aa5 1 - Y3 Ab3 b12, 1925-1935, undated (Box 212, Folder 216)
        - Y3 Ab3 b13 - Y3 Ab4 9, 1925-1934, undated (Box 213, Folder 217)
        - Y3 Ab4 10 - Y3 Ab8 13, 1916-1934, undated (Box 214, Folder 218)
        - Y3 Ab8 14 - Y3 Ae5 24, 1926-1935, undated (Box 215, Folder 219)
        - Y3 Ae5 25 - Y3 Am7 8, 1925-1935, undated (Box 216, Folder 220)
        - Y3 Am7 9 - Y3 As6 rm26, 1926-1932, undated (Box 217, Folder 221)
        - Y3 As8 c1 - Y3 Br28 1, 1923-1934, undated (Box 218, Folder 222)
        - Y3 Br5 w1 - Y3 S1 7, 1926-1933, undated (Box 219, Folder 223)
        - Y3 S1 8 - Y3 S3 24, 1915-1935, undated (Box 220, Folder 224)
        - Y3 S3 25 - Y3 S6 2, 1915-1926, undated (Box 221, Folder 225)
        - Y3 S6 3 - Y3 Tp4 1, undated (Box 222, Folder 226)
      - Yosemite National Park
        - Y7 Ad3 1 - Y7 Ae5 1, 1924-1925, undated
        - Y7 Bg88 So1 - Y7 S3 14, 1924-1933, undated (Box 223, Folder 227)
        - Y7 S3 15 - Y7 Ts3 2, 1923-1926, undated (Box 224, Folder 228)
      - Zion National Park
        - Z7 Am8 1 - Z7 S1 15, 1924-1925, undated
        - Z7 S1 16 - Z7 S3 6, 1920-1928, undated (Box 225, Folder 229)
        - Z7 S3 7 - Z7 Tl 1, 1923-1925, undated (Box 226, Folder 230)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Misc. Ab3 g1 - Misc. Fp43 g1, undated
        - Misc. Fr9 1 - Misc. Mt4 11, 1924-1925, undated (Box 227, Folder 231)
      - Loose Items Removed from Above Boxes
        - Holograph list of Alaskan birds and flowers seen in 1927 found folded in front of A2 Bc7 1, Birds of Alaska slides (Box 228, Folder 232)
        - Holograph notes on geology of Bryce Canyon found folded in front of B8 Fc5b 1, undated (Box 228, Folder 233)
  - UNCLASSIFIED LANTERN SLIDES
    - Panoramic Lantern Slides
      - Mt. Assiniboine Environs, Alberta, Canada, 1921 (Box 229, Folder 234)
      - Lake Og - Mt. Assiniboine, Alberta, Canada, undated (Box 229, Folder 235)
      - Range from Wonder Pass, Alberta, Canada, undated (Box 229, Folder 236)
      - Fording the Kananackia, Alberta, Canada, 1921 (Box 229, Folder 237)
      - Bryant Creek Valley, Alberta, Canada, 1921 (Box 229, Folder 238)
      - Lawson Lake, Jellicoe Glacier, Alberta, Canada, undated (Box 229, Folder 239)
      - Pallisar Pass, Alberta, Canada, 1921 (Box 229, Folder 240)
      - Blue Bells, Hidden Lake, Alberta, Canada, 1921 (Box 229, Folder 241)
      - Blue Bells, Hidden Lake, Alberta, Canada, undated (Box 229, Folder 242)
    - Other Lantern Slides
      Numbers in parentheses are the number of slides in a box
      - Alaska (5), 1927, 1935 (Box 230, Folder 243)
      - Arch Canyon, Utah (4), 1925 (Box 230, Folder 244)
      - Bryce & Zion Canyons, Utah (5), 1925, undated (Box 230, Folder 245)
      - Bryce Canyon, Utah (5), 1925, undated (Box 230, Folder 246)
      - Canadian Rockies (10), 1926-1933, undated (Box 230, Folder 247)
      - Colorado River Trip (7), 1925 (Box 230, Folder 248)
      - Colorado River Trip (6), 1925 (Box 230, Folder 249)
      - Colorado River Trip, (6), 1925 (Box 230, Folder 250)
      - Crater Lake, Oregon (1), 1923 (Box 230, Folder 251)
      - Glacier Park, Montana (8), 1926 (Box 230, Folder 252)